<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyStats - University</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="closed">Closed</string>
    <string name="fulltime">Full time courses</string>
    <string name="parttime">Part time courses</string>
    <string name="satisfaction_title">How satisfied previous students have been with the course can be a good indication of what your experience will be like on the course. Click the sections below to find out the percentage were satisfied with the enclosed statements</string>



    <string name="about_app_title">MyStat University</string>
    <string name="basic_intro">The MyStats application was created to make an easy way to find different courses from specific universities within a certain area.
    The app was created by students for students, parents and teachers to easily find out the facts about different courses and universities.
    </string>

    <string name="meet_the_team_intro">The team first met as they all attended Teesside University. This page tells everyone a little about each person who contributed to the making of this app.</string>
    <string name="chris_personal">This is Chris, a 27 year old meditating pescatarian, previously in business in the renewable sector;  Chris realised his true calling was in programming and problem solving after he built a SAP calculator making income predictions based on post code solar radiation levels.  Chris is studying Computer Science and aims to continue his education to Msc with interests in Machine Learning.</string>
    <string name="tel_personal">This is Terry, after working in McDonalds until the age of 23 he decided it was time to pursue his dream of computer coding. In his spare time Terry enjoys playing pool. Terry is about to start a placement at Sabisu. Terry aspires to work as a software developer once he finishes his degree course.</string>
    <string name="dan_personal">This is Daniel, he is currently 26 and is from Stockton on Tees. Daniel is currently in his third year of a five-year degree studying BSc Computing (with foundation and placement year). Daniel is due to start a placement with Nissan this June. Daniel previously served 9 years with the Army Reserves and deployed to Afghanistan in 2012 and 2014 before deciding on a career change. Daniel aspires to become a software developer for a large organisation such as Nissan. </string>
    <string name="jack_personal">This is Jack, he is currently 21 and from Darlington. Jack is currently studying for his bachelor’s degree in computer science at Teeside university. Next year he is due to embark on a work placement at redev development in Leeds. This will be his first time working in the industry and is an exciting opportunity. This opportunity should help him reach his long-term career goal of joining the software industry as a software engineer.</string>

    <string name="data_intro">This section explains where the MyStats Application collects the information and how it is used. The application stores the information in firebase database and returns any relevant complete course sets. </string>
    <string name="hesa">The main amount of information is collected by the Higher Education Statistics Agency (HESA) and stored in a database on the HESA website. It receives the information mainly from the different university in which course it is displaying the information about. This agency collects as much information as it can about each course, some courses however have certain pieces of information missing. MyStats only shows courses with complete information. www.hesa.ac.uk</string>
    <string name="national_student_survey"> The MyStat app uses data from the National Student Survey to collect satisfaction information about the different courses from the students, this is done by Ipsos MORI. This information is collected through a questionnaire containing 22 questions and an additional 6 questions for NHS students. If the questionnaire hasn’t been completed by 10 students on a course, then the information isn’t included. For more information please visit the NSS website at http://www.thestudentsurvey.com</string>
    <string name="dlfh">The Destination of Leavers from Higher Education is used to find the information about people who have recently left university. The DLHE asks the leavers of courses what they are doing roughly 6 months and has an 80 response rate after the course has finished, they then survey the same people 40 months later with a 40 response rate.</string>

    <string name="copy_page_intro">On this page, you can find the legal stuff about the data used on MyStats</string>
    <string name="copy_unistats_disclaimer">MyStats is in no way affiliated with the UniStats website and uses and supplies the information without conjunction with the UniStats website.</string>
    <string name="copy_hesa_disclaimer">All the information is taken from the HESA database the data is published under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International Licence. This means you can use and adapt this content for personal and commercial use, but you must give appropriate credit, provide a link to the licence and indicate if you have made changes. Appropriate credit should include our name (HESA) and web address (www.hesa.ac.uk). HESA is not responsible for any the conclusions or way the data is represented on this app and is not responsible for any content on this app.</string>







    <string name="ucas_tips_intro">Applying for University can seem a daunting task, so here at MyStats the team have found the best tips they can to help create your route as easy and successful as possible.</string>

    <string name="ucas_tips_choosing_course_intro">So, first things first, deciding which course it is you want to take. Do you have a certain job in mind? This decision will help to shape the whole of your application form. You have most likely considered this however with over 37000 courses on offer in over 350 different universities it sometimes isn’t the easiest of choices. Therefore, we at UniStats have found the best points for you to consider</string>
    <string name="ucas_tips_career">Career: Do you have a certain career in mind? Perhaps you can talk to someone who is already in that career about how they got into the career. See a career guidance councillor at school or college. </string>
    <string name="ucas_tips_hobby">Hobby: If you haven’t a specific career in mind have you got a certain area in which you would like to go into something that you are passionate about. Considering a specific area can help to decrease the amount of options drastically.</string>
    <string name="ucas_tips_entry_requirments">Entry requirements: So, you have decided on a course or an area of courses but let’s be totally realistic for a second, do you have the grades or will you get the grades? If no, then this may not be the course for you. However, make sure to look at mature student, foundation years or special circumstances, MyStats gives a good overview of what students usually have when they apply for a certain course at a certain university. </string>
    <string name="ucas_tips_location">Location: You know the course, you feel like you have the grades but still don’t know what university to go to, maybe you should consider these points. How will you do being far away from home? Is there a city that you would just love to live in? Do you know someone who is already at a certain university? Try to consider these points.</string>
    <string name="ucas_tips_modules">Modules: Finally, you have narrowed it down, you have an idea of the type of course or career you want to take, you think you can get the grades or have looked at another entry way and have a few different universities to consider, well you need to make sure you look at the modules the course has to offer. Some courses may be similar but might have modules that cater to your needs and your overall needs.</string>






    <string name="entry_info_introduction">Everyone needs to know how many UCAS points they need to get into their favourite Uni, Below you will see a chart that shows the spread of what last years students had when they started this course</string>

</resources>
